freedownloadsapps.com 2016-12-19

# Privacy Policy - freedownloadsapps.com

  * Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to freedownloadsapps is important to us.  
freedownloadsapps is serious regarding the privacy of Internet users because our business success depends upon our ability to maintain the trust of our users. 

**Personal Information**

At freedownloadsapps, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important.  
Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit freedownloadsapps,   
and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

 **Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.   
The information in the log files include your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit   
our site, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **Cookies**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user.   
Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.   
Some of our partners use cookies on our site (for example Google Adsense). However, we have no access  
to or control over these cookies. Please refer to their privacy policies for details. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site   
and other sites on the Internet.   
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

**How to Contact Us**

Should you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy , please use our contact form.
